<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>web on My New EPIC Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://tunalad.github.io/tags/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in web on My New EPIC Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:21:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tunalad.github.io/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>vue-kanban</title>
      <link>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/vue-kanban/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 21:23:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/vue-kanban/</guid>
      <description>Trello-inspired task management web app. A full stack web app that I built as my graduation project, and a tool that I personally use sometimes.
Besides creating a kanban board app, I wanted to make an actual FOSS alternative to the paid task management apps. So this app can be used by multiple people for actual projects, and they will all get updated when changes to the board are made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vue-floppy-sim</title>
      <link>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/vue-floppy-sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:19:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/vue-floppy-sim/</guid>
      <description>This web app was born from a music project that I planned. Idea was to create an album using Sonic Pi and put it onto a floppy disk. So we just take the Sonic Pi code we wrote, and put it on a floppy disk. I also very much wanted to use some samples, so I would have to manage how many samples I can fit on there. And this is pretty much what the tool was meant to help with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vue-todo</title>
      <link>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/vue-todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:21:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/vue-todo/</guid>
      <description>Todo app, the app most people make when trying out new tools. It was made for me to figure out what are the ways about saving data locally.
There&amp;rsquo;s nothing much going on with this app, just add, check, or delete tasks in the list. It does what it has to do.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
