<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gui on My New EPIC Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://tunalad.github.io/tags/gui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gui on My New EPIC Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 22:31:15 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tunalad.github.io/tags/gui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PDF-splitter</title>
      <link>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/pdf-splitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 22:33:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/pdf-splitter/</guid>
      <description>PDF-splitter is a user-friendly GUI tool designed to extract pages from a PDF document. GUI part was done via Qt, so (in theory) it should work on all systems
Originally developed as a project for the SCS (Specialized Computer Systems) course, it continues to receive occasional updates.
1. Usage The process is straightforward: locate a document and load it. Upon loading, each page of the document is converted into an image (as depicted above).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lixling</title>
      <link>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/lixling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 22:24:24 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/lixling/</guid>
      <description>Lixling: A minimalistic plugin manager for Lite XL, inspired by vim-plug.
The goal of this project was to create a small and straightforward plugin manager for Lite XL, free from dependencies on external Lua modules or programs (except for git), ensuring seamless integration with the text editor.
1. Usage 1.2 Commands Let&amp;rsquo;s start by unraveling the commands:
Command Description Lixling: Install Installs listed plugins Lixling: Update Updates listed plugins Lixling: Upgrade Updates Lixling itself Lixling: Clear &amp;ldquo;Exiles&amp;rdquo; unlisted plugins Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick breakdown:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>weatherman</title>
      <link>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/weatherman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 22:31:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tunalad.github.io/projects/weatherman/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t have any screenshots for this app because I don&amp;rsquo;t have Android Studio installed. Yes, I could install it, but the tool is massive and I have no interest in writing Android apps. Android Studio is also a massive resources hog, so I&amp;rsquo;d prefert to not have it on my system.
This post exists for the future me to update with the app&amp;rsquo;s explanation and images. How far in the future?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
